http://www.childcaremanager.com/company/privacy.aspx

Home  Products & ServicesDiscover what your center has been missing!ProductsChildcare ManagerTime ManagerTimeKlockServicesRapidTuitionCCM OnlineInvestmentPricing  SupportDocumentsDownloadsExtended Support Plan  Contact  CompanyAbout UsTerms of ServicePrivacyWarrantiesReturn PolicyLegal  Free Demo
Company / Privacy
You are here: HomeCompanyPrivacy
PerSoft Online Privacy Policy
At PerSoft, we are dedicated to revolutionizing the way professional childcare providers manage their businesses. To that end, we respect and protect the privacy of those who visit or use our Web sites. We want you to know how your information is used. To demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices, we have adopted leading industry privacy guidelines.
Visiting PerSoft Online
When using our sites, you may get information, access online products and services, communicate with us or link to other websites with which we do business. While doing that, you may give us information that can be used to enhance the products and services we provide you. This online privacy policy describes how we use and protect the information that you share with us. This policy governs websites owned and operated by Personalized Software. Our policy does not govern websites of other parties to which we may provide links, because Personalized Software is not responsible for the Web privacy practices or content of those sites.
Our Philosophy & Practice
We understand that it is important for you to have confidence in our privacy practices in order to fully participate in our online offerings. Therefore, here are the principles that govern our information practices and other privacy aspects of our Web sites:
Our information practices will be posted on each Website.
Provisions will be made to allow visitors and users of our Websites to update or correct the personally identifiable information provided us.
Every effort will be taken to protect personally identifiable information from loss, misuse and unauthorized alteration.
Various ways will be provided for you to contact us about our information practices and other privacy aspects.
Information Collected on Our Website
Our Web server automatically attempts to collect general, non-personally identifiable information for each visitor to our site. This information may include the name of the visitor’s domain, the pages visited, and from which site the visitor came.
Certain pages on our website, including requests for evaluation software and product literature, prompt users to enter information into an online form. This information is used by Personalized Software for the purpose of satisfying customer requests.
Billing information collected for orders using online ordering is collected to process the order. Visitors will be asked to re-enter this information each time they visit the site. For security reasons, Personalized Software does not save it with personally identifiable information.
Use of Information Generated From Our Website
Credit card information is used only for the purpose of processing an order. Personalized Software will never use this information for other purposes.
Information provided to Personalized Software through its Web site will not be released, sold, bartered, or traded to any individual outside of Personalized Software or authorized resellers.
Updates
The Personalized Software privacy policies are subject to change without notice. Changes to this policy will be reflected in this statement.
Feedback
Feedback on this privacy statement and the policies it reflects is always welcome and appreciated. Submit any feedback to:
Persoft Inc.
General InquiriesP.O.Box 359Phoenix, OR 97535-0359(800) 553-2312 toll-free(541) 535-8085(541) 535-8889 faxinfo@childcaremanager.comBusiness HoursMonday–Friday7am to 4pm PSTSaturday, SundayClosed
More Information
About Us
Terms of Service
Privacy
Warranties
Return Policy
Legal
